dmipartners.com 2017-10-21

# Privacy is our Concern - DMi Partners

DMi Partners, Inc. and the CPA Café (collectively, “DMi”) respects the privacy of our customers and is serious about protecting your online privacy. This policy will explain how we gather and use personal information submitted by in response to marketing offers available at the CPA Café and DMi’s website (the “Sites”). Therefore, by interacting with these Sites, you are agreeing and accepting this policy.

The CPA Café is owned and operated by DMi. The CPA Cafe is a network of third party business partners’ websites. Such websites may use cookies and/or other data collection tools. DMi is not responsible for the privacy practices, policies or the content of such websites. DMi encourages everyone to read the posted privacy policies whenever interacting with any website to learn more about the privacy practices of that website. DMi has no control over the use of any information by third party websites, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any PII. Similarly, while DMi contractually requires that our business partners adhere to law and industry self-regulatory codes such as those offered by the NAI, DAA, and eDAA, DMi does not have access to, or control of, the cookies and/or other data collection tools that may be placed on any advertisement by a third-party. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies and/or other data collection tools by any third party.

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [info@dmipartners.com](mailto:info@dmipartners.com).

### Information Collected:

DMi Partners collects the following types of information:

  * Personally Identifiable Information we collect from you on applications and forms completed on our Sites as well as from additional sources used to process your request.
  * Information while you browse our Site. While you view our Site, our system tracks the referring url, the pages you view, the pages you download and your IP address. Additionally, the CPA Café and/or a third-party business partner may place a “cookie” on your computer that tracks your use of their sites. Please see section below for more information on cookies.
  * We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”) via third party sites. Non-PII cannot be used to contact a particular person or entity. Non-PII may include your IP address, pages viewed on the third-party sites, browser type, Internet Service Provider, the time/date of your visit to the Sites or the third-party sites, and your computer’s operating system (e.g., Windows XP). DMi uses this information for internal purposes such as to help our business partners optimize their marketing efforts, improve and customize their Site, and to track site usage.

### How We Use That Information:

DMi reserves the right to use this information provided by you for:

  1. the specific purpose for which such information was provided (including sharing the information with third-party business partners);
  2. personal, demographic and profile data to improve our site;
  3. our marketing and promotional purposes;
  4. as disclosed at the time such information is provided; and/or as disclosed in this Policy.

Although, it is important to note that DMi reserves the right to change or modify this policy at any time with or without notice. If you have any questions regarding the use of your information or about this policy, please feel free to contact us at [info@dmipartners.com](mailto:info@dmipartners.com).

DMi may share your information with its service providers such as email service providers and chat providers, and with your permission, any other entities that we believe are able to provide you with special opportunities and offers.

DMi may also occasionally license, share, or otherwise disclose data we collected to third parties. DMi does not have control over such party’s information handling practices and is not responsible for any failure of such party to adhere to this Policy.

Additionally, DMi may disclose your information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the applicable laws; (b) protect and defend the rights, interests and property of DMi; and (c) comply with the valid legal process.

Upon your submission of your information, DMi and its business partners may choose to contact you to discuss the interest you have expressed via your submission of a form. By submitting the form you are consenting to be contacted by DMi and its third-party business partners, by telephone (landline or cellphone), email, SMS messaging, direct mail and any other forms of communication.

### Analytics Tools:

We use analytics tools and other third party technologies, such as Google Analytics, DARC, Cake and DoubleClick cookies, to collect non-personal information in the form of various usage and user metrics when you use our Sites. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, and other similar information.

The third party analytics companies who collect information on our Sites and/or Services and other online products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.

In addition to our use of technologies as described herein, we may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to you based on your use of the Sites or the offers provided by our business partners and to otherwise collect and use data about you your use. For more information about this practice, please see the “Third Party Advertising Technologies” section below.

You may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or you may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page.

### Cookies:

DMi and/or a business partner may place a “cookie” on your computer that tracks your use of our Site and other sites in our network. A cookie is a string of data that is stored on your hard drive, which enables DMi and out business partners to analyze the performance of websites and marketing campaigns. Cookies can enrich your browsing experience by allowing sites to learn your preferences or allowing you to avoid signing in every time you visit certain sites.

### Framing:

DMi and our business partners may have webforms where the form is framed within their site. However, you are actually on a third party website and should be aware that you are entering information on a third party site. Some pages may have the look and feel of being on our site, however the information collected on these pages may not be covered under our privacy statement. All information collected on that site is owned and controlled by that company’s privacy statement.

### Links to Other Sites:

If you click on a link to a third party site, (including on an advertisement), you will leave our Sites and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personally identifiable information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy practices as DMi. We encourage you to review the privacy statements of any other service provider from whom you request services.

### Web Beacons:

If applicable, the Sites and our business partners’ sites may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

### Widgets:

If applicable, the Sites and our business partners’ sites may include Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying product information, the news, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.

### Registry Compliance:

By submitting your personal and/or financial information on the Sites and our business partner’s sites, you are hereby granting written permission to us, and our disclosed third party business partners to contact you using the information you volunteered. You are consenting to receive telephone calls (landline or cell-phone) from DMi and its third-party business partners, and thereby, you waive your right to file a claim with the FTC or any other agency in regards to these contacts or calls. You agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR ß310 et seq.) (the “Rule”), as amended from time to time.

### Security:

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews:

DMi and DMi’s business partners may post customer testimonials/comments/reviews which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer’s consent with a signed release of liability or via email or phone prior to posting their name with the testimonial/comment/review.

### Third Party Advertising Technologies/Remarketing:

In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, we also may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to users and to collect and use other data about user activities (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third party services). These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior. These companies may use information about user behavior in order to provide customized advertisements across various services and products. In the course of providing these services, products or placing advertisements, these third party companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer, and may record information to these cookies based upon your activities on any of our Site and/or services and on third party websites. Each of these companies uses this cookie information according to their own privacy and security policies. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out as indicated in this Policy. Please note this does not opt you out of being delivered advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### We do not collect Information from Children:

The information and services provided by us are not intended for children under the age of eighteen (18) years old. Additionally, we do not direct our Sites to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13) years old. If DMi learns of a person who registers on this site who is under the age of thirteen (13) years old, we will immediately delete that person’s information.

### California Privacy Rights:

Under California law, site visitors who are residents of California may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at the information below.

### Transfer, Sale, or Assign:

At its sole discretion, DMi may transfer, sell, and/or assign information collected on and through the Sites, including but not limited to, the users personal information collected, to one or more third parties, as a result of the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization, or liquidation of DMi.

### Data Retention:

We or business partners will retain your information. If you wish to request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at DMi. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Updates to Our Privacy Policy:

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. If we make a material change regarding how we use your personal information, we may notify you of the existence and location of the new or revised policy through email or by posting the changes online at our site.

### Contact Information:

Please e-mail questions or requests for more information about DMi’s privacy policy at [info@dmipartners.com](mailto:info@dmipartners.com) or write to us at:

**DMi Partners, Inc.**  
1 South Broad Street  
11th Floor  
Philadelphia, PA 19107  
Attn: Legal Department

Updated June 1, 2014
